# Dillon Stock

Agile Software Engineer with 3.5 years of industry experience building single-page, client facing Angular web applications, and REST APIs. Fluent in TypeScript (Angular & NodeJS), C# and Python. Seeking an agile work environment focused on building cloud-native, containerized applications leveraging DevOps and open-source technologies.

14110 Foothill Ln Golden, CO 80401 (248) 568-9596 dillon.w.stock@gmail.com DillonStock.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Rocket Mortgage**, Remote — *Software Engineer*

**April 2020 - PRESENT** 

# TypeScript (Angular & NodeJS)

- Fully owned major package version updates of NX, Angular and NodeJS
- Built custom RxJS operators, bundling transformation & error handling into logical groupings for easily testable observable pipelines
- Extended Angular logging library with custom logging service, injecting application state into log items; crucial for debugging and reproducing Splunk errors
- Built pipe to interpolate variables inside CMS content, replacing them with dynamic data from RESTful services, granting content authors maximum flexibility
- Built robust, generic and reusable Google Places Autocomplete component, leveraging both synchronous and asynchronous input validation
- Built RESTful API controllers to integrate with web services & built SQS client wrapper to submit to AWS queue
- Built configuration API endpoint, along with Angular's dynamic component loader to facilitate runtime configuration

# C# .NET

- Integrated with mortgage rates API; modeled and transformed JSON response for web component consumption
- Implemented Author Details pages on RocketMortgage.com with .NET Razor templates
  CircleCI
- Added job to CI/CD pipeline to audit web performance with Google's open-source
  Lighthouse CI tooling, and updated job status upon completion using GitHub's API

# **Urban Science**, Detroit — Associate Software Engineer

August 2018 - April 2020

- Converted 12 web pages from legacy proprietary framework to RESTful .NET web API consumed by Angular frontend
- Designed reusable and abstract Redis caching pattern to improve performance of a read-heavy REST API
- Designed and implemented a new class hierarchy for MVC controllers, abstracting away 6000 lines of redundant code

#### **EDUCATION**

# Michigan State University — B.S. Computer Science, 3.5/4.0 GPA

May 2015 - May 2018

- Utilized AWS SDK for Python (Boto3) to interact with and manage AWS services such as S3, Comprehend, and Transcribe
- Built Python deployment packages for AWS Lambda functions, and configured various triggers including API Gateway, CloudWatch events, and S3 file uploads

#### **SKILLS**

Angular

**NodeIS** 

**TypeScript** 

Python

Git

**AWS** 

C#

Docker

Linux

# **SOFTWARE/TOOLS**

VS Code

Postman

GitHub

**AWS Console** 

CircleCI

Microsoft TFS

### **AWARDS**

Design Day Praxis Award -Most technically challenging Capstone project

Dean's List - Spring 2017, Fall 2016